myprogress.in 2012-09-03

# :: Pro Online Marketing Pvt. Ltd. ::

Privacy Policy

## Success

Improvement is an ongoing process. Pro Online Marketing Pvt Ltd has always strived to achieve the motto of our group - 'Together We Prosper', by improving the quality of our products and keeping in touch with the latest trends in the market. To this end, our research and development process is always online to meet our customers needs and expectations.

This privacy policy only covers the Pro Online Marketing Pvt. Ltd.’s website [ **http://www.MyProgress.in**](http://www.myprogress.in/) and all other 'Top Level Domains' attached to the domain name “MyProgress.in”. External websites linked from this site are not covered by this policy.

Pro Online Marketing Pvt. Ltd. takes your privacy very seriously.

**Information That We Collect From You**   
When you visit, register or order products or services on this site you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself including your name, contact details and credit or debit card information. We may also collect information about your usage of our website as well as information about you from messages you post to the website and e-mails or letters you send to us. To maintain customer service standards and to assist staff training, we may record and monitor incoming calls.

**Use or Disclosure of Your Information**   
Pro Online Marketing Pvt. Ltd. does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Pro Online Marketing Pvt. Ltd. under extremely strict confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Pro Online Marketing Pvt. Ltd. communicate with you about offers from Pro Online Marketing Pvt. Ltd. and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

  * We have a parent's permission to share the information if the user is a child under age 13.

  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise required by law.

  * We transfer information about you if Pro Online Marketing Pvt. Ltd. is acquired by or merged with another company.

We will make a sincere effort to respond in a timely manner to your requests to correct inaccuracies in your personal information. To correct inaccuracies in your personal information please return the message containing the inaccuracies to the sender with details of the correction requested.

You may choose to give us personal information, such as your name and address or e-mail id that may be needed, for example, to correspond with you, to download our white papers or to provide you with a subscription. If you tell us that you do not want us to use this information as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes. We intend to protect the quality and integrity of your personally identifiable information.

**Cookies, and other technologies**   
We sometimes collect anonymous information from visits to our sites to help us provide better customer service. For example, we keep track of the domains from which people visit and we also measure visitor activity on Pro Online Marketing Pvt. Ltd. web sites, but we do so in ways that keep the information anonymous. Pro Online Marketing Pvt. Ltd. or its affiliates or vendors may use this data to analyze trends and statistics and to help us provide better customer service. We maintain the highest levels of confidentiality for this information, our affiliates and vendors follow the same high levels of confidentiality. This anonymous information is used and analyzed only at an aggregate level to help us understand trends and patterns. None of this information is reviewed at an individual level. If you do not want your transaction details used in this manner, you can either disable your cookies or opt-out at the download or request page.

**Mailers**   
Pro Online Marketing Pvt. Ltd. may, if you so choose, send direct mailers to you at the address given by you. You have the option to 'opt-out' of this direct mailer by way of links provided at the bottom of each mailer. We respect your privacy and in the event that you choose to not receive such mailers, we will take all steps to remove you from the list.
